# Cinzia Isabel Ferrari

# multidisciplinary design researcher

I am an Italian design researcher with a natural curiosity for interdisciplinary projects. I operate comfortably in areas that are unknown, bridging across disciplines in the search for better futures for todays' problems - through design innovation.

cinziaisabelferrari@gmail.com

cinziaferrari.com

PDF portfolio

London / Eindhoven / Milano

+39 3459136480

## **Education**

CENTRAL SAINT MARTINS UAL Master of Arts in Biodesign / Merit / 2021

CODE FIRST: GIRLS / Twitter London Web Development / Oct 2019 - Apr 2020

POLITECNICO DI MILANO Bachelor of Science in Interior Design / 2014

# **Experience**

WEB DEVELOPER AND UX / UI DESIGNER

Freelance, 2020 - 2021 Website developer and UX/UI consultant for freelance projects.

MULTIDISCIPLINARY CREATIVE Freelance, 2017 Jewelry design, Collage and Illustration design.

PRODUCT AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER In The Box. Verona / 2014 - 2016 Design of jewellery packaging and window display.

#### **Technical Skills**

Adobe Ai Ps Id Xd Pr Ae

Figma / Miro

Cinema 4d / Rhinoceros

HTML5 / CSS / Javascript

## **Exhibitions**

MILAN DESIGN WEEK Sept 5 - 10 2021 / Spazio Gamma, Milano

ISOLA DESIGN FESTIVAL 2021 Online / April - Oct 2021

ICADE CONFERENCE 2021 Online / Oct 2021

MA BIODESIGN WEBSITE

**UAL GRADUATE SHOWCASE 2021** 

ARTS THREAD Global Design Graduate Show 2021

**FASHION CROSSOVER LONDON** 

BIOSUMMIT CONFERENCE 4.0 Biocreation station 2020

# Talks / Press

Creative Speaker at Adidas Digital Strategy Team

Colour Hive X CSM

Webinar: Exploring Biomateriability

MA Biodesign Symposium 2021

#### **Awards**

BEYOND PLASTIC AWARDS 2020 Bronze prize / Most Innovative Project